Preliminary Guide to the Hannah Green Papers M1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Accession 1998-249
  - Manuscripts
    - Notebook: September 11, 1972 or 1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: 4671 - The Year of the Ox - February 3, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Notebook: June 2, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: October 21, 1974 Mas de St. Jerome (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: February 1, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: Notes, alternate notebook - beginning May 27, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Notebook: Mas de St. Jerome December 1, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: New York - September '77 - Barrow St. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: April 12, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: November 30, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Notebook: Cambridge notebook 1979 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: September 10, 1979 at Conques (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: March 4, 1980 Barrow St. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: December 14, 1980 Conques (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Notebook: June 26, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: Conques - August 25, 1982 My Book of Pilgrimage (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: Summer 1984 - Conques (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: June 17, 1985 - Conques (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Notebook: December 1986 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: December 1986 - also Conques July 4, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: August 10, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: Summer 1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Notebook: June 1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Notebook: Summer 1993 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Notebook: Neahtawantah - August 1994 (Flat-box 48)
    - Notebook: Dreams and Early Memories (Flat-box 49)
    - Notebook: "Lisbon: from a writer's notebook - a fiction" (Flat-box 50)
    - Notebook: The Book of Saint Foy - Barrow St., June 7, 1976 (Flat-box 51)
    - Notebook: Notebook II for The Book of Saint Foy (started Feb.21, 1978) (Flat-box 52)
    - Notebook: Notebook III -- "Golden Spark, Little Saint (started end Feb 1980)" (Flat-box 53)
- Series 2: Accession 1999-170
  - The Dead of the House
    - The Last of My Grandfather's Wine (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Last of My Grandfather's Wine (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Last of My Grandfather's Wine (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Last of My Grandfather's Wine (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Notes on The Death of My Grandfather (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Dead of The House (Draft) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Dead of The House (Draft) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Dead of The House (Draft) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Notes on The Death of My Grandfather (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Dead of The House- Proposal (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - New Yorker- October 11, 1969 (published version of Dead of the House) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - The Dead of the House (Draft) (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - The Dead of the House (Draft) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Dead of the House (Draft) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Dead of the House (Hand-Written Notes) (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Notes on The Death of My Grandfather (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Old Degolyer Manuscript with Notes (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - The Dead of the House (Hand-Written Draft) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Dead of the House (Hand-Written with notes) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Dead of the House (Hand-Written with notes) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Dead of the House (Hand-Written with notes) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Dead of the House (Draft with Notes) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Dead of the House (Draft with Notes) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - The Dead of the House (Draft with Notes) (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - The Dead of the House (Draft) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The Dead of the House (THe New Yorker Copy) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Dead of the House (Short Story Copy) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - the Dead of the House (Full copy) (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - the Dead of the House (Full copy) (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - the Dead of the House (Full copy with Edits) (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - The Dead of the House (Copy sent out for Opinion) (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - The Dead of the House (Multiple Partial Chapters) (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - The Dead of The House (Full Copy) (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Grandfather's Last Wine (Partial Copies) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Pages from: Here Tecumesh Fell, Grandfathers Last Wine (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Summer Afternoon, Summer Afternoon (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The Dead of The House (3 Copies) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Introduction for The Dead of The House (Hungarian Version) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Dead of the Hosue (Draft) (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - The Dead of the House (Full Copy) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Writing Organization- Early Book release Recipients (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Grandfather's Last Wine (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - The Death (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Excerpt from Grandfather's Last Wine (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - The Dead of the House (Partial Draft) (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Notes on the Death of my Grandfather (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - The Dead of the House (Draft) (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Last of My Grandfather's Wine (Edited Gallies) May 12, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - The Dead of the House (Edited Gallies) 1966 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - The Dead of the House (Edited Gallies) 1966 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - The Dead of The House (Proofs) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Dead of The House (Proofs) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Saint Foy
    - Les Chapiteaux de Conques photocopy (Flat-box 26, Folder 3)
    - Hand Written notes on Saint Foy (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Page by Page notes on Saint Foy (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - A Brief Description of Saint Foy (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Reviews and Notes on Saint Foy (Box 7)
    - Saint Foy Partial Drafts (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Multiple Chapters from Saint Foy (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 3rd Section of Chapter 2: Saint Foy (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Conques; from Saint Foy (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Golden Spark, Little Saint (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Saint Foy: Chapter 3 with Edits (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Golden Spark, Little Saint (Multiple Drafts) (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Golden Spark, Little Saint (2 Copies) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Saint Foy (Partial Drafts) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Golden Spark, Little Saint (Draft) (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Saint Foy (Partial Draft) (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Saint Foy (Partial Draft) (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Saint Foy (Partial Copy) (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Saint Foy (Full Copy) (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Saint Foy (Draft Pages) (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Saint Foy Draft Pages with Edits (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Notebook - 1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Saint Foy (Draft) (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Saint Foy (Drafts) (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Saint Foy (Partial Draft) (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Saint Foy (Partial Drafts) (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Saint Foy (Partial Draft) (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Photocopies of articles by Jean Taralon, etc. & other bibliographic notes (Flat-box 26, Folder 2)
    - Drafts from "Golden Spark" Mostly "Rainbow Section" of Chapter 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Short stories & other writing
    - The Last of My Grandfather's Wine (Drafts) (Box 3, Folder 1-18)
    - Notes on The Death of My Grandfather (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - The Matterhorn (Drafts) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Kroupa's (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Ghost's Holiday (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Mister Nabokav (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Sphynx and the Pyramid (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - In Praise of John Wesley (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The Particular Man, Somewhere In the Ruins, A Bit About the Cat, Venice, The Grey Bird (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - At Hindenberg Kaserne (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - At Hindenberg Kaserne (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Want (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Summer Afternoon, Summer Afternoon (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Voices from Summers Past (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Fires (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Notes on: Dawn Powell (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Journal of a Death (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Material from- A Literary Circle (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Pigtails & Scissors, The Literary Circle, In the City of Paris, Martin, Sisters, Mischievious Pig (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Summer Afternoon, Summer Afternoon (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Summer Afternoon, Summer Afternoon (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Summer Afternoon, Summer Afternoon (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - College Days (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Dreams and Early Memories (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Natalie (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - The Unicorn, In Her Ring's Radiance, Kroupa- The Dog Who Couldn't Help It (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - In The City of Paris, A Place Something Like the Moon, Gordon, Alter Ego (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Letter From Germany & Interview with Feodor, Sanjarovski (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - The Matterhorn (Drafts) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Short Stories: Tatian, Natasha, Lorelie, A Bit about the Cat, Pool (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Prospectus for Natalie Stories (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Somewhere In the Ruins (Draft) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Old Degolyer Manuscript With Notes (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Grandfather's Last Wine (Hand-Written) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Old Canoe Trip Notes (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Here Tecumesh Fell (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Kolya (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Heather, Man with a Gun, Alter Ego, Natives of Africa (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - The Unicorn (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Suzanne (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Background on "The Unicorn" (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - The Hermit of Shark Tooth Shoal, Old Joe, The Unicorn, 3 Untitled Stories (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Gallies- Kolya (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Misc. Short Stories Untitled (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - A.G Riddle (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Rochester, UFO, The Grey Bird (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - "The Virgin Mary" from Snow (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Kolya (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Death of Hang on Sloopy (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - The Sphynx and the Pyramid (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - The Sphynx and the Pyramid (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The Lovebound by Adele Wiseman (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Grandfather's Last Wine (Galley) (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - The Town (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Kolya & A Voice Heard in Ramah (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Kolya & A Voice Heard in Ramah (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Kolya (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Kolya, The Literary Circle, Fraulein Schwarz, Untitled (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Grandfathers Last Wine with Edits (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Notes from Grandpa Green's Letters (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Old Degolyer Manuscript (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Birthday Party, Save One for Mainz, A Hot Night (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Mi-No-Pa-Mo-Disin (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous annotated typescripts - early writing and family recollections (Box 27, Folders 2-3)
    - In the Grip of Terror annotated typescript (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence 1940's (Box 13, Folder 1-15)
    - Germany - Youth Workcamp Documents (1950) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence from Gaby 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Letters to Hannah from Poolie 1957 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Letters to Hannah from Poolie 1957 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence to Hannah Green 1948 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence to Hannah 1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence from Peter Martin 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Poetry by Thomas Kinsella (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Wellesley Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Peter Wessel Friends of Conques: Mayer's Destruction (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Merry Christmas to Hannah Booklet (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Hannah Green Correspondence to Parents 1948 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Letters to Hannah's San Francisco Residence (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Blank Postcards (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Hannah Green Correspondence- 1950's (Box 16, Folder 1-9)
    - Correspondence 1944-1948 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Wellesley Correspondence 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Wellesley Correspondence 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Wellesley Correspondence 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Wellesley Correspondence 1945-1946 (Box 14)
    - Wellesley Correspondence 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Wellesley Correspondence 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Hannah to John Morrison 1946 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - No dates (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence- No Dates (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Family Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Family Correspondence 1946 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Family Correspondence 1946 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Family Correspondence 1947 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Family Correspondence 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Family Correspondence No Dates (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Family Correspondence 1942 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Hannah's Correspondence to Mom & Dad 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1949 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1948 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1950-1953 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence 1960 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1960 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Hannah's Correspondence to Mom 1968 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1945 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1940's (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1940's (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence 1950's (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence 1940's - 1950's (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence from Hannah to Parents 1940's (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1950's (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1950's (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence 1950's (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1960's (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1960's (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1970's (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - No Dates (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence from Hannah to Parents 1966 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence from Hannah to Parents 1948 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1930's - 1940's (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1940's - 1950's (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1940's - 1950's (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence 1940's - 1950's (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Personal Materials
    - Personal Correspondence to Hannah Green (Box 22, Folder 1-21)
    - Correspondence with Stephen Spender (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Hannah Green Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Hannah Green to Poolie Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Hannah's Correspondence from Lonsdale (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Misc. Hannah Green Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - John Wesley Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Hostage Crisis Correspondence: Hannah to Hodding Carter III (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence to Wallace Stegner (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Rejection Letter to Hannah Green (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Hannah Green Business Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Hannah Green Business Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Hannah Green Business Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Hannah Green Business Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Steve Miller Letters (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Unsent Letters to Bob from Hannah (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence from Unlce Joe to Hannah (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence from Hannah to Parents (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence from Hannah to Parents (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Hannah Green to Poolie Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Contains Personal and Family Photographs as well as Green Family Correspondence (Box 9, Folders 1-36)
    - College Class Notes (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Personal Notes (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Personal Notes (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Miniature Personal Notebooks (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Personal Notes (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Personal Notebook 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - College Notebooks (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Person Address Books (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Person Address Books (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Person Journals 1942-1944 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Daily Planners 1948, 1978, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Daily Planners 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Daily Planners 1962-1967 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Russian 101 Notebooks (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Russian 201 Notebook (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Vincent McHugh: Plans (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Poetry Carbons by Vincent McHugh (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Personal Correspondence: Hannah Green to Thomas Kinsella 1964 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Personal Correspondence to Hannah 1964 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Personal Correspondence to Hannah 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Letters 1957 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Letters 1957 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Letters 1957 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Letters 1957 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1959 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1959 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1959 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1957 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Vincent McHugh Correspondence 1958 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Confidential Letter to Matthew Green (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Patents and Trademarks in Foreign Affairs Presentation (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - James Albert Green Eulogy (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Hannah Green's Will (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Hand -Written Notes 8/10/67 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - The Magic Train (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Green Family Photographs (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Hannah's Passports (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Wedding Invitations for Hannah (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Mary Allen & James A. Green Documents (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Hannah's Personal Papers (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Hannah's Milestone Book (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Family Photographs (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Family Photographs (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Family Photographs (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Family Photographs etc. (Flat-box 26, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Also includes photo collage with classmates, Green's prep school diploma dated June 1944, and a print depicting a pre-Civil War Glendale, Ohio.
    - Cincinnati newspapers (possibly with Green family references), 1913, 1930, 1952 (Flat-box 26, Folder 4)
  - Teaching Materials
    - Writing Workshop Materials (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Writing Workshop Materials (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Hannah's Teaching Material (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - San Jose State Composition Book 1948 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Lecture Materials (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Lecture Materials (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Lecture Materials (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Notes on Mark Twain (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The New Yorker- October 11, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Articles by Hannah from Germany (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Poems with Notes (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Poems with Notes (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Articles by Hannah from Ulm, Germany (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Writings (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Poetry (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Poems (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Misc. Poems (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Letters to Mr. Cowley about The Dead of the House (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Misc. Pages of Writing (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Short Stories from Misc. Authors (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Pictorial Mysteries (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Book Prospectus (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - A Family Story (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Mary Elvira Stevenson Scholarship Thank-you Letter (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Misc. Writing Drafts (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Raymond Chandler by Frank MacShane (Chp. 1-3) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Raymond Chandler by Frank MacShane (Chp. 4-7) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Raymond Chanlder by Frank MacShane (Chp. 8-11) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Works of Thomas McGonigle (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Sophie So Far Away by Taylor Morris (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Anna LMNO by Sarah Glasscock (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Tillie's Silences (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Life in the Iron Mills by Rebecca Harding Davis (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - It Happened 'Round the North Bend (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Poems (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Fulbert of Charters and the Cathedral School (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Misc. Hannah Green Papers (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Hannah Green Papers (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Hannah Green Papers (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Hannah Green Papers (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - NENS Clippings (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - NENS Clippings (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Clippings from Germany (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Reprints and other publications (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - cassette, phonograph record (Box 27, Folder 6)
      audiocassette labeled "Stegner/"For Jack especially Oliver Sachs"; signed copy of Hank Decato's "Salute to Gene Autrey" single
- Series 3: Accession 2012-064
  - Golden Spark, Little Saint manuscript by Hannah Green pages iii-87 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Golden Spark, Little Saint Manuscript by Hannah Green pages 88-183 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Golden Spark, Little Saint Manuscript by Hannah Green pages 184-284 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Golden Spark, Little Saint Manuscript by Hannah Green pages 285-370 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Golden Spark, Little Saint Manuscript by Hannah Green pages 371-471 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Little Saint Manuscript by Hannah Green pages ii-13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Little Saint Manuscript by Hannah Green pages 14-91 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Little Saint Manuscript by Hannah Green pages 92-207 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Little Saint Manuscript by Hannah Green pages 208-278 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hannah Green's Notes and Manuscript for Little Saint pages 2-63 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hannah Green's Notes and Manuscript for Little Saint pages 64-160 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Hannah Green's Notes and Manuscript for Little Saint pages 161-240 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hannah Green's Notes and Manuscript for Little Saint pages 241-319 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Hannah Green's Notes and Manuscript for Little Saint pages 320-351 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Golden Sparks, Little Saint Manuscript pages 1-53 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Golden Sparks, Little Saint Manuscript pages 54-140 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Golden Sparks, Little Saint Manuscript pages 141-210 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Golden Sparks, Little Saint Manuscript pages 211-275 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Golden Sparks, Little Saint Manuscript pages 276-377 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Golden Sparks, Little Saint Manuscript pages 378-470 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Dead of the House pages iii-63 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Dead of the House pages 64-147 (Box 1, Folder 23)